亲爱的 你在干什么
Honey, what are you doing?
我看了一个超赞的有关念力的视频
I just saw this incredible telekinesis video.
我在努力让一片培根浮在空中
I'm trying to make a piece of bacon levitate.
话说 你不需要工作吗
Don't you have to, I don't know, work?
你是说我永远不可能成功吗
Are you saying it'll never happen?
就没有更委婉美好的说法吗
Is there perhaps a more colorful way of saying that?
我知道你是想让我说
I know you're trying to get me to say
"等猪飞起来也就成了"
"It'll happen when pigs fly."
这也算吧
That counts.
什么
What?
天啊
Oh, my gosh!
早上好 地球同胞们
Good morning, Earth mates.
早上好 法...
Morning, Farr--
我的下背部疼死了
Oh, my lower back is killing me.
有谁看到我的治愈水晶了吗
Has anyone seen my healing crystal?
那可能是我们唯一没见到的你的"东西"了
That may be the only thing of yours we haven't seen.
迪兰的妈妈法拉过来看宝宝
Dylan's mom, Farrah, came to see the babies,
然后她发现她的四角关系
and then she found out that her polyamorous quad
被降格成了三角关系
was downgraded to a triad.
现在我们摊上她甩不掉了
Now we're stuck with her.
四角啊 浮想联翩 你能想象吗
Polyamory. Can you imagine?
不能
No.
她必须赶紧滚
She needs to go.
法拉 法拉
Farrah! Farrah!
法拉
Farrah!
你非得在这里干这个吗
Do you have to do that right here?
很抱歉
Oh, I am so sorry.
我没意识到你希望
I didn't realize you wanted it
菲律宾一直洪水泛滥呢
to keep flooding in the Philippines.
我不希望菲律宾一直洪水泛滥 克莱尔
I don't want it to keep flooding in the Philippines, Claire.
-没事 我换个房间 -好极了
- It's okay. I'll just go in the other room. - Great.
是杰瑞 我不能接
It's Jerry. I can't.
他肯定会唠叨45分钟 说他有多想念妈妈
It's gonna be 45 minutes about how much he misses Mom
然后透露过多关于他们性生活的私密内容
and then some overshare about their sex life.
克莱尔 他是家人
Claire, he's family.
杰瑞
Jerry.
你还好吗
How are you?
是啊
Yeah.
不 我懂 我们也很想她
No, I know. We miss her, too.
宝宝们都很好
The babies are great.
是啊 不断地在探索这个世界
Yeah, constantly exploring,
总是把手指伸进各种地方
always sticking their fingers in everything.
天啊 那可真是...
Oh, whoa, yeah, what a --
真是关于我已故岳母的有趣画面
what a fun image of my late mother-in-law.
真的吗
Really?
我看看我们到时候在不在
Let me just -- Let me just check to see if we're gonna be around.
杰瑞要沿着蝴蝶迁徙路线去墨西哥
Jerry is following the butterfly migration to Mexico
他想明天过来跟我们打个招呼
and wants to stop by tomorrow to say hi.
不可能 赶快编个借口
No way. Make up an excuse.
我很不擅长撒谎
I'm a terrible liar.
那可糟了
Tough.
家里绝对不能再多个嬉皮怪人了
The last thing we need around here is another hippie kook.
这一天终于来了 我变成跟我爸一样的人了
Oh, it finally happened. I'm my father.
天啊 你在这儿啊
Oh, my goddesses, there you are.
克莱尔 你愿意
Oh, Claire, would you be comfortable
用这个在我的屁股上方来回擦几次吗
rubbing this just above my buttocks
我要唱一曲西藏疼痛赞歌
while I offer up a Tibetan pain chant?
那听上去不像我会做的事
Doesn't sound like me.
但我或许认识个人能帮到你
But I might know someone who could help you out.
说实话 杰瑞 那个...
Honestly, Jerry, it's that, uh...
克莱尔和我最近很不顺
Claire and I have -- have hit a rough patch.
她已经吃了...好几罐生奶油了
She's been huffing... cans of whipped cream.
我是说...
I mean...
快搭救我
Help me.
我们的床下
Underneath our bed
简直就像吃馅饼大赛的后台
looks like backstage at a pie-eating contest.
-邀请他过来 -什么
- Invite him here. - What?
尽快把他弄过来 快点
Just get him here as fast as you can. Come on.
实际上 杰瑞 一切都好
Uh, actually, Jerry, everything's fine.
克莱尔刚刚同意寻求医生的帮助了
Claire just agreed to seek help.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
刚刚是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
杰瑞很寂寞 法拉也很寂寞
Jerry's lonely, Farrah's lonely,
他们都来烦我们
they both glom onto us.
我们给他们牵线搭桥 他们就可以烦彼此了
We set them up, they'll glom onto each other,
让他用"鼓棒"慢慢敲她的"鼓"吧
and then she can bang his drum.
我美丽的天才
My beautiful genius.
抱歉 等一下
Oop, sorry. Hold on.
现在只差帮你也找个奇葩搭伙了
Now I just have to find someone to set you up with.
要把好东西拿来招待客人了吗
Oh, breaking out the good stuff, huh?
你知道吗
Well, you know what?
我们终于跟一对拉拉情侣成为密友了
We're finally close friends with a lesbian couple,
我希望她们能感到被我们珍惜
and -- and I -- I want them to feel as special to us
就好像她们是真正的同性恋一样
as if they were real gays.
小卡 她们跟我们一样是同性恋
Cam, they're just as gay as we are.
稍等 马上就好
Okay, hold on. One moment.
-好了 -跟我差不多 没你这么基
- Bink! - Okay, well, as I am.
好了
Okay.
-嗨 -天啊
- Hi. - Oh, my gosh.
你们真是超有爱的一家
You guys are such a cute family.
天啊 那张照片
Oh, gosh, that picture.
那是在一个游乐场拍的
That was taken at an amusement park.
那并非真正的大脚怪
That's not the real Bigfoot.
"真正的大脚怪"
"Real Bigfoot,"
-天啊 你真是太搞笑了 -好吧 那行
- Oh, my God. You're so funny. - Yeah. Sure. Okay.
就当"他是在开玩笑"吧
Let's go with "He was making a joke."
话说 说到家庭...
So, you guys, speaking of families...
我们也想组建个家庭
We're thinking of starting one of our own.
-太棒了 -恭喜
- Amazing. - Congratulations.
你们打算怎么做 有什么计划
Oh, how are you gonna do it? What's the plan?
实际上 我们正想找你们取取"经"呢
Actually, we wanted to ask you something about that.
每个基佬人生中的某一刻
Eh, there comes a point in every gay man's life
都会遇到拉拉妇妇向他寻求精子
when a lesbian couple asks him for his sperm.
-除非你是米奇和我 -是啊
- Unless you're Mitchell and me. - Yeah.
我们所有的朋友们都被人找过
All of our friends have been asked,
而我们却被残忍地无视了
while we have been cruelly overlooked.
心好痛
It's painful.
那就像未被选中去玩踢球
It's like not getting picked to play kickball.
我倒是从没遇到过这种情况
Well, that never happened to me.
我曾是踢球队的队长
I was my kickball team's captain.
不过那是在大球星伤了腿 不得不被安乐死后
Well, only after our star broke his leg and had to be put down.
-它是... -一头驴子
- He was a -- - A mule.
早猜到了
From a mile away.
来吧 想问什么都行
Go ahead. Ask us anything.
你知道我们对你们的评价很高
Well, you know we think the world of you guys.
-是吗 -我们对你们也一样
- Yes? - And we, you.
首先
First of all,
如果我们不领养 你们会对我们有看法吗
would you judge us if we didn't adopt?
那很自私吗
Is that selfish?
-不会 -当然不会
- Um, no. - No.
真让人松了一口气
Oh, that's such a relief.
接下来的一步
Now, the next step
就是找一个...
is finding someone who can --
捐精的人
Donate?
没错
Yes.
我们不希望跟对方有经济上或别的牵扯
You know, we don't want anyone involved financially or otherwise,
所以我们打算去找精子银行
so we were just thinking of going to the sperm bank.
那是个好的选择
That's a good option,
但一定要确保门卫很帅
but make sure the janitors are handsome,
因为他们有进入任何地方的钥匙
because, you know, they have the keys to everything.
我们还考虑过用我哥哥的精子
Well, we also thought about asking my brother.
你不会想选择这个方向的
Oh, you don't want to go down that road.
太复杂了
It's too complicated.
"是爸爸 又是舅舅 是爸爸 又是舅舅"
"My daddy, my uncle, my daddy, my uncle."
简直是电影《唐人街》的翻版
It's "Chinatown."
没错 你们最好找一个
Yeah, you want someone that --
不那么亲近的人
you know, with a little distance,
你们认识 且熟悉
that you know and -- and trust.
长得帅气 身体健康
Who's attractive and healthy.
家族里至少一代半
And who hasn't had mental illness in their family
没有精神疾病
in at least a generation and a half.
那真如美梦一般
Well, that's the dream.
美梦也是可以成真的
Well, dreams can come true.
天啊 谢谢你们
Oh, my God. Thank you, guys.
不 是谢谢你们
No, thank you.
如果你们想到了合适的人 能告诉我们一声吗
If you think of someone, will you let us know?
-死拉拉 -死拉拉
- Lesbians. - Lesbians.
这是你的卡布奇诺
Here's your cappuccino.
我就不喝了
None for me.
我不需要精神抖擞地体会
I don't need to be sharp to experience
生活没有雪莉·桃久奇后的空虚
the empty void that is life without Sherry Shaker.
牛奶里拉的这画是什么
What are these little drawings in the milk?
是我凭窗远眺的画面
That's me staring out a window.
那些星星是用我的眼泪做的
I made the stars with my tears.
宝贝 如果你能够在我开了三个街区后
Ay, papi, if you can survive me driving three blocks
才发现你在我车顶且活下来
with you on the roof of my car,
那这次你也能撑过去
you can survive this.
那是几时发生的
When did that happen?
你跟雪莉本来就不会有好结果
It wasn't gonna work out with Sherry anyway.
她是加拿大人
She's Canadian.
他们钱币上印着鸭子
They have ducks on their money.
牛奶装在袋子里卖
They sell milk in a bag.
有需要再来我房间找我吧
I'll be in my room if anyone needs me.
我骗谁呢 根本没人需要我
Who am I kidding? No one needs me.
宝贝 失恋这种事会自己拨乱反正的
Ay, papi, these things have a way of working out.
我保证
I promise.
你保证
You promise?
你干了什么好事
What did you do?
我找了人帮忙
I called in a favor.
卢克
Luke!
又来 我们不是扯平了吗
Again? I thought we were even.
我要你为曼尼做一件事
I need you to do something for Manny.
那对他非常重要
It'll mean the world to him.
行吧
Okay, I guess.
我要你去雪莉的即兴表演
I want you to go to Sherry's improv show,
对她说曼尼的好话
talk him up to her.
我要她后悔跟他分手了
I want her to regret breaking up with him.
不 绝对不行
No. Not that.
唯独即兴表演不行
Anything but improv.
即兴表演和被施水刑没什么区别
Improv is no different than getting waterboarded.
你只要保持冷静
Just stay calm,
心里想着让你快乐的地方
go to a pleasant place in your mind,
并且谨记你不是真的快死了
and remember that you're not actually dying.
好吧 我去
Fine. I'll do it.
乖孩子
Good boy.
继续睡吧
Go back to sleep.
你为什么带撬棍来
Why'd you bring a crowbar?
没原因呀
No reason.
歌洛莉亚 我们不该插手
Gloria, we should not be involved.
你知道我每次失意时
You know what my dad always said to me
我爸都对我说什么吗
every time I was down?
什么都不说
Nothing.
我学会独自解决所有问题
I learned to figure everything out on my own.
这是你最缺乏魅力的特质
This is your least attractive quality.
你的同理心呢
Where is your empathy?
我有同理心啊
I have empathy.
就是关心在乎别人的意思 对吧
That's the one where you care about people, right?
你不愿意为任何人付出
You don't go out of your way for anyone.
我愿意啊
Yes, I do.
你记得俱乐部那个泊车小弟吗
You remember that little valet at the club?
如果我没有害他被炒鱿鱼
If I hadn't got him fired,
他现在还在帮人移座椅靠背呢
he'd still be moving everybody's seats up.
来啦
Okay, here we go.
家传秘方的杏子酱
Some apricot jam from an old family recipe.
虽然你们对我的"家传秘方"不会有兴趣
Not that you would be interested in any of my family recipes.
出什么事了吗
Is everything okay?
你们为什么不想选我们当捐精者
Uh -- Uh -- Why don't you want us to be your donor?
没关系 直说了吧
It's okay. Just say it.
-你们反感我的红发 -还是讨厌他的雀斑
- You're put off by my red hair. - Or is it his freckles?
-还是因为我容易晒伤 -或是因为他的...
- Or my tendency to burn. - Or is it his --
-你就不能说个你的缺点吗 -行吧
- Can this one please be about you? - Yeah, yeah.
等等 你们意思是愿意捐精给我们吗
Wait, are you saying that you would donate for us?
老实说 我们很希望这样
Honestly, we would love that,
但又怕让你们为难
but we were afraid to put you on the spot,
而且我们以为你们不会答应
and we didn't think you'd say yes.
-我们当然会答应啊 -我们很喜欢你们
- Oh -- Well, of -- of course we'd say yes! - We adore you!
莫莉 我们好像找到孩子的爸爸了
Oh! Molly, I think we just found our daddy.
-天啊 -太好了
- Oh, my God. - Okay.
那你们想要我们中的哪一个
Okay, so, which one of us do you want?
我不知道 我们都还没机会
I don't know. We haven't even had a chance
-考虑这个 -是啊
- to think about it. - Yeah.
要不要我们绕场一圈
Well, would it be helpful if we, you know, walked around
让你们欣赏一下我们 从肩部到小腿
so you could take us in from shoulder to shank?
这又不是在县集市卖猪
It's not the county fair.
好吧 那要不我们出去外面
Alright, well, maybe we'll just go outside
踢点什么 看看腿劲儿
and, I don't know, kick something?
或者我们比赛拼拼图
Or -- Or we could do a puzzle?
或是看谁会拼写"康涅狄格州"
Or we could spell Connecticut?
不如你们俩决定吧
Why don't you guys just decide?
我们要哪个都行
We're -- We're happy either way.
应该没问题
Shouldn't be a problem.
很好 你们俩都在家
Oh, good, you're both here.
听着 我思考了昨天的事
Listen, I was thinking about yesterday,
你很难过
how upset you are,
你也说我不关心别人的感受
and how you say I don't care about people's feelings,
所以看好了
so check this out.
布兰蒂 进来吧
Brandi, get in here.
我还没抽完烟
I'm not done with my cigarette!
你干了什么好事
What did you do?
我之前一直在想
I was trying to figure a way
如何能帮曼尼走出失恋阴影
how to help Manny to move on,
突然之间 我就遇到了这位小天使
and all of a sudden, I met this little angel.
白兰蒂
Brandi?
等等啦
Hold on!
滤嘴那部分才最带劲儿啊
The best part's right at the filter!
你们会喜欢她的
You're gonna love her.
她在洗车店负责管理抹布
She runs towels at the car wash.
-你为什么支持他乱来 -我没...
- Why did you encourage this? - N--
明明还有"白兰地"
Hey, now, why settle for Sherry
何必单恋"雪莉酒"
when you can have a little Brandi?
我承认 这双关挺机智
I'll admit, that's good.
我勒个大操
Holy
这房子太屌了
This house!
难怪你能付得起火山岩打蜡
So, this is how come you can afford the lava wax.
白兰蒂 这是我妻子歌洛莉亚
Brandi, this is my wife, Gloria,
这猛男是我儿子曼尼
and this stud is my son, Manny.
白兰蒂 你一定是个好女孩
Brandi, I'm sure you're very nice,
但我才刚失去一生挚爱 还没走出来
but I'm dealing with losing the love of my life,
我还需要点时间
and I just need some time.
我懂你现在的心情 亲
I know what you're going through, honey.
我男人看了《徒手攀岩》电影
My man saw "Free Solo"
就决定去攀登本地银行这座高山
and tried to scale the local bank.
他为做他最热爱的事而死
He died doing what he loved --
就是挑衅警察敢不敢开枪打他
daring the cops to shoot him.
杰 我是在这里臭骂你呢
Jay, should I scream at you here,
还是去厨房臭骂你
or should we do it in the kitchen?
我正好想吃点零食啦
I could go for a little snack.
听着 你们先彼此熟悉一下
Uh, listen, you guys get to know each other.
曼尼 去吧台给她调杯饮料
Manny, offer her a drink at the bar.
有含肉桂的吗
You got anything with cinnamon?
我这人不挑 什么都行
I'm not particular.
你想什么呢
What were you thinking
居然带这种女孩来家里
bringing a girl like that here?
你说什么胡话呢
What are you talking about?
白兰蒂可有意思了
Brandi's a ton of fun.
当然了 也许她不是带回家见妈妈的类型
Oh, sure, maybe you don't bring her home to Mom.
你不就是带她回家见妈了吗
That's literally what you did.
希望敲门的是她的假释官
I hope that that's her parole officer.
卢克
Ah, Luke!
真是惊喜耶
What a surprise!
你和雪莉谈得怎么样
How did your talk with Sherry go?
不太顺利
Not well.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你有没有告诉她《房产兄弟大挑战》其中一个兄弟
Did you mention to her that Manny was retweeted
转发了曼尼的推特
by one of the Property Brothers?
有 我提了这事
Yeah, I brought that up.
她怎么说
And what did she say?
她想念他吗
Uh, does she miss him?
她愿意和他复合吗
Will she take him back?
-我看不会了 -为什么
- I don't think so. - Why not?
我们...
Well, we kind of...
接吻了
kissed.
什么
What?
找白兰蒂来这招
Well, the Brandi plan's
现在看来很不错 对吧
looking pretty good right now, huh?
家人们好啊
Hello, family.
杰瑞 欢迎 你好吗
Oh. Hi, Jerry. Welcome. How are you?
抱歉 我本想敲门的 但你们也知道我痛恨暴力
Sorry. I would've knocked, but you know I abhor violence.
抱歉
Oh sorry,
我午饭时磨杂粮煮粥来着
I was grinding polenta for our lunch.
所以胳膊有点酸痛
My arm's kinda tender.
真有"杂粮粥肘"这种病
Polenta elbow is a real thing.
玛丽安·威廉姆森是唯一一个
Marianne Williamson was the only candidate
有勇气谈论此事的总统候选人
with the guts to talk about it.
杰瑞 你过得还好吗
So, Jer, how you doing?
坚持挺住呗
I'm hanging in there.
见到你们俩我很高兴
Very happy to see you both.
但事实就是 克莱尔 在这灯光下
But the truth is, Claire, in this light,
你看起来真像你母亲
you're reminding me so much of your mother.
-是因为发型吧 -因为颈纹
- Well, it's the hair. - Same neck.
你就是杰瑞吧
Oh, you must be Jerry.
我是迪兰的妈妈 法拉
I'm Dylan's mom, Farrah.
很高兴认识你
How wonderful to meet you.
我就直说了 我喜欢拥抱
Full disclosure -- I'm a hugger.
抱歉 拥抱让我不自在
I'm sorry, I'm not very comfortable with that,
因为我喜欢亲亲
because I'm a kisser.
这项链真漂亮
Oh, what a lovely necklace.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
这是日本捕鲸船的残骸做的
It was made from the wreckage of a Japanese whaling ship.
为世人献上俳句的民族
How can the same people that gave us the haiku
居然忍心捕杀这么优雅的生灵
want to hunt such a graceful creature?
我可以保证
Uh, well, I can guarantee
没有蔬菜收到伤害
in the making of this salad.
克莱尔 其实科学已经证明植物也有痛觉
Actually, Claire, it's been proven that plants feel pain.
是的 从地里拔出来时它们会惨叫
Yes, they scream when you rip them from the ground.
那这些葡萄的遭遇
Oh, um, then you're gonna hate
肯定会让你们很痛心
what happened to these grapes.
没关系 它们都醉了
That's okay. They're drunk.
今天天气可真好
Well, it is such a nice day outside.
不如你们两个去后院品酒
Why don't the two of you enjoy your wine in the backyard
这里交给我们布置
while we finish setting up in here?
多美好的想法
What a lovely idea.
法拉 你知道吗
Oh, Farrah, did you know
杰瑞正在追随蝴蝶迁徙
that Jerry is following the butterfly migration?
一直追随到墨西哥吗
All the way to Méjico?
整个冬天和春天
I'm gonna spend the winter and spring
我都会在钦夸山脉保护区吊床露营
hammock camping in the Sierra Chincua sanctuary.
那是我在地球上最爱的地方之一
That is one of my favorite places on this Earth.
-你去过吗 -许久没去过了
- Oh, you've been there? - Not in ages,
但我真想在这一世去看看
but I would love to visit in this life.
进展得比我们希望得还顺利
This is going so much better than we even hoped!
太诡异了 杰瑞就喜欢那个类型的
It's so weird. Jerry has such a type.
法拉和我妈简直
I mean, Farrah and my mom are the --
我妈 她在后院
My mom. She's in the backyard.
对了
Ohhhh, right.
老天
Oh, God.
我不知道是怎么回事
Um, I don't know what happened.
是迪迪
It's Dede.
她怎么会在这
How did she get here?
她不是在米奇尔家吗
I thought she was at Mitchell's house.
我没听懂
I don't understand.
我妈的骨灰和树根融合在一起了
My mom's ashes are fused to the roots of the tree.
毫不意外
Of course.
迪迪
Dede,
我永远不会当着你的面与其他女人调情
I never would have flirted with another woman in front of you.
除非是我们的开放周末
Unless it was that kind of weekend,
就像在陶斯那次
like that time in Taos.
迪迪需要我
Dede needs me.
我哪也不该去
I shouldn't go anywhere.
可是你不去看蝴蝶了吗
But-But what-But what about the butterflies
还有墨西哥
and Mejico?
克莱尔 我能感觉到
Claire, I can feel it.
你母亲现在很痛苦
Your mother is in pain right now.
我们能确定那是树的痛苦吗
Are-Are we absolutely sure it's the tree?
因为我有份奶酪茄子正在备受煎熬
Because I do have an eggplant parmesan under the broiler.
我不想小题大做
I don't mean to overreact,
但我想这种情况 我们有必要喉唱一曲
but I think the situation may call for some throat singing.
开始吧 米奇 小卡
Alright. Mitch. Cam.
-好 我先说 -好
- Okay, I'll go first. - Okay.
-我长得高 -高
- I'm tall. - Tall.
我很强壮
I'm strong,
我有马特·达蒙同款鼻子
and I have a Matt Damon nose.
-得了吧 -那好
- Okay. - Okay.
米奇尔 快说 是我还是马特·达蒙
Mitchell, quick -- me or Matt Damon?
别多想 快回答
Don't think, just answer.
-好吧 这个给你写上 -当然
- Okay, I'll give you that one. - Yeah.
好 到我了
Um, alright, now me.
完美音高
Perfect pitch.
这个宝宝需要的是节奏感
Well, what this baby needs is rhythm.
我一个龋齿都没有
And I've never had a cavity.
我写字好看
I-I have good penmanship.
我有个姨妈活到了110岁
Well, I had an aunt that lived to 110,
她还每天抽烟斗
and she smoked a pipe every day.
-我很负责 -我很会带孩子
- I'm responsible. - I'm nurturing.
我也很会带孩子
Okay. I'm nurturing, too.
莉莉还是宝宝时 我每晚都唱歌哄她睡觉
When Lily was a baby, I sang her to sleep every night,
用完美音高唱
with perfect pitch.
以前每天早上送她上学后
Well, I used to look at her through the window every morning
我都透过窗子看着她
when I would drop her off at school,
直到保安拍了我的照片留证
until the security guard took my picture.
好吧 这样吧
Okay, uh... you know what?
由你来捐
You-You be the donor.
我觉得我做不到身为某个孩子的父亲
I don't think that I can have a kid in the world
却对孩子的生活不管不问
and not be a part of their life.
米奇尔 我觉得我也做不到
Oh, Mitchell, I don't think I can, either.
我的美鼻孩子成为史上第一个美式足球弃踢手
It would kill me to have a little button-nose beauty out there
或是第一个火箭舞蹈队男队员而名震天下
kicking up a storm as the first female punter
而我却不能相认 我会难受死的
or the first male Rockette.
还是我们求人家的
We begged them.
我们会看起来特别不靠谱
We're gonna look like such flakes.
他们会心碎的 我们该怎么告诉人家
They're gonna be heartbroken. How do we tell them?
我们只能彻底坦白
We're just gonna have to be completely honest.
我们可以说微波炉出故障
We could tell them the microwave's been on the fritz
害我们不育了
and we're both sterile.
很好 就这么说
Great. That. Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
是我们
It's us.
好惊喜
What a surprise.
亲爱的 米奇和小卡来了
Uh, honey? Mitch and Cam are here!
我们很抱歉这样冒昧上门
Listen, we're sorry for dropping in like this.
-但有些事我们得告诉你们 -是的
- Uh, but there's something we need to tell you. - Yeah.
你们好吗
What's up?
这件事真的很难开口
Okay, there-there's no easy way to say this.
我们不太能接受捐精
Um...we're just not comfortable donating sperm.
听我们解释
And-And-- You know, listen,
我们真的深感荣幸
we were so flattered.
但我们可能只是一时上头了
But I think we just got caught up in the moment.
我们理解
Oh, we get it.
是的 没关系的
Yeah. No problem.
-真的吗 -完全没关系
- Oh, really? - It's totally fine.
十分感谢你们过来通知我们
Thank you so much for letting us know.
你们人最好了
You guys are the best.
当然
Oh. Oh, yeah.
-那好 -祝你们今天愉快
- Okay. - Hey, have a good one.
-当然 -再见
- Sure. - Bye. Bye.
真不敢相信这么顺利
Wow, I-I can't believe how well that went.
是啊 我感觉好多了
Yeah, I know. I feel-I feel so much better.
简直太顺利了
That was...so easy.
是啊 真的好顺利
Yeah. Yeah, like, really easy.
等等 过于顺利了吗
Wait, was it too easy?
交给我
I got this.
-我们又回来了 -是啊
- It's us again. - Yeah.
刚才是怎么回事
Listen, um... what just happened?
因为我们刚刚破坏了你们的整个生育计划
Because we just cratered your entire family planning,
而你们只说了句"祝我们今天愉快"
and all we get is a "Have a good one"?
你们好像一点也不难过
You don't seem too broken up about it.
不 我们特别伤心
No, no, we're super-sad.
我们拉拉就这样
We're just lesbians.
-当然 -是我们不好
- Oh, of course. - Okay. That's on us.
-怪我们 -好了
- That is on... - Okay.
是谁在笑
Who's that?
-是坎贝尔 -才不是
- Campbell. - No, it's not.
你才是笑起来像男人的那个
You're the one with the masculine laugh.
我也突然意识到
Yeah, and I'm-I'm suddenly aware
我们站在门外聊了好久
that we've been talking outside for a long time.
你介意我们进去坐坐吗
Do-Do you mind if we come in?
完全不介意 米奇和小卡
Yeah, no, not at all, Mitch and Cam!
快请进屋
Come on into the house!
坎贝尔
Hey, Campbell!
这位猛男是谁
Who's-Who-Who's your hunk?
我是内森
I'm Nathan.
内森
Nathan.
你好 内森 这是
Hello, Nathan. What is...
香槟 怎么 你们在庆祝什么吗
Champagne. What? Were you celebrating?
和一个有着非凡基因的男人
With a man in possession of some pretty remarkable genetics.
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
所以我们放弃了你们也毫不在乎
That's why you let us off the hook so easy.
你们本来就不打算用我们了
You were gonna replace us.
我们很抱歉
Okay, we're sorry.
是的 精子会由他来捐
Yes, he's gonna donate.
我们也不是计划好的 我们刚认识
We did not plan this. We just met.
-你们刚认识 -刚认识
- You just met?! - Just met?
-在哪 怎么认识的 -几点 怎么认识的
- Where? How? How? - When? How?
他是我们的滴滴司机
He was our L-Lyft driver.
他的车非常干净
Man, his car was really clean,
他特别会聊天
he made excellent conversation.
看看他啊
And I mean, look at him.
你们明白的 对吗
You guys get it, right?
这基因确实该广泛播种
That should be making babies.
至少我们能告诉朋友们 有人找过我们
Look, at least we can tell our friends that we were asked.
是啊 你知道吗
Yeah, and you know what?
作为第二名也挺好的
Hey, second place isn't bad.
-是的 -没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你介意吗
Ooh, do you mind?
我们可以跟你合个影吗
Can we get a-a picture with you
让朋友看看 得多强大的对手才能打败我们
just to show all of our friends what it took to beat us out?
-没问题 -麻烦了 谢谢
- Sure. - Sorry. Thanks.
-来吧 -我脱掉上衣会不会更好一些
- Okay. - Would it help if I took off my shirt?
-应该吧 是啊 -好太多了
- Oh, probably, yeah. - In so many ways.
绝对能帮上忙 来吧
Yes, it would. Here.
-露出来啦 -秀出来了
- There is it. - Okay. There --
好货亮出来了
Wow. There...it is.
好的
Okay.
你亲雪莉干嘛啊
Why would you kiss Sherry?
我也不是有心的
I didn't mean for it to happen.
我一点都不意外
I'm not surprised.
我看你跟玩具土豆先生亲热过
I've seen you make out with a Mr. Potato Head.
是土豆太太好吗
It was a Mrs. Potato Head.
她有蝴蝶结跟擦了口红的嘴唇
She had the bow and the girl lips.
表演开始前我没机会跟她说到话
I couldn't talk to Sherry before the show,
所以我只能坐等
so I had to sit through it.
她的第一段演出烂透了 我本来想逃跑
The first sketch was so bad, I tried to bail,
但他们把出口都锁上了
but they locked the doors.
当她再度走上台时
Then she walked on the stage --
或者我该说是
or should I say,
第一位章鱼总统走上台了
the first octopus President walked on stage.
快看
Look.
她能一次签署8条法案
She's signing eight bills at once.
而且我永远不会签到笔没"墨"
And I'll never run out of ink.
她的演出仿佛环法自行车赛
Her performance was a Tour de France.
她就像是火辣女版的我爸爸
She was like a hot, girl version of my dad.
演出结束后 我们聊得很开心 然后就发生了
Afterwards, we kept talking, and...it just happened.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry,
但我想我可能对她产生了感情
but I think I may have real feelings for her.
听我说 你以后再也不许见她
Listen to me, you're never going to see Sherry ever again.
我得跟曼尼坦白
I have to tell Manny the truth.
你敢
Don't you dare.
坦白什么
Tell me what?
曼尼 对不起 但我... 亲了雪莉
Manny, I'm sorry, but...I kissed Sherry.
我觉得很过意不去
I feel terrible about it.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我会的
I will be.
等我把你打死我就舒坦了
After I kick your ass!
-给我过来 -赞啦
- Come on! - Oh, hell yeah!
等等 等等
Hold on, hold on!
曼尼 暴力永远不能解决问题
Manny, violence is never the answer.
孩子 你不知道你这会造成什么后果
Kid, you don't know what you're doing.
我当然知道
Uh, yes, I do.
我得初级武戏课可是拿了"尚可"
I got a "Satisfactory" in Beginning Stage Combat.
开演
And action!
-卢克 你过来 -别这样
- Come here, Luke. Luke! - No, easy, easy.
你别这样
Whoa! Easy!
-你冷静 -你怎么能这么对我
- Easy! - How could you?!
-全天下那么多女人你偏去搞她 -停手停手停手
- Of all the women! Come on, Luke! - No! No! No! No!
别打了
Ah! No!
够了
Enough.
听我说 你很伤心我也很难过
Now, listen, I'm sorry that you're hurting so badly,
我让你走出那段感情的计划很失败
and I'm sorry that my plan to help you move on
我也很抱歉
was a disaster.
但你是个有广阔胸襟的好男人
But you're a good guy with a big heart,
你会找到真命天女的
and you're gonna find the right person,
我向你保证
I promise you.
而你呢 你勇敢
And you... it was big of you
跑来跟曼尼面对面坦白做得很棒
to want to tell Manny the truth to his face.
-谢谢 -但你越界了
- Thanks. - But you crossed a line.
你只想到自己而辜负了家人
You put yourself in front of your family,
你还伤了一个视你如手足的男人
and you hurt a guy who loves you like a brother.
你这么做让我非常失望
You disappointed the hell out of me.
我得请你离开了
I'm gonna ask you to leave.
对不起 曼尼
I'm sorry, Manny.
别难过了 宝贝
Sorry, papi.
我可能得麻烦你让我独处一会儿了
I think I need to be alone for a while.
我理解
I understand.
曼尼 你要记得
Just remember, Manny,
当你碰到雨天时 我都愿意陪伴你
I'm there for you whenever there's a rainy day.
因为那些日子不用工作 所以...
'Cause we don't work those, so...
孩子 你要挺起胸膛
You keep your chin up, kid.
一切都会关关难过关关过
It's gonna work out okay.
我知道
I know.
谢谢你 杰
Thanks, Jay.
对不起我之前说你从不在乎别人
I'm so sorry that I told you that you didn't care about other people.
我当然在乎别人啦
I care about other people.
我内心也很敏感啊
I'm really very sensitive.
那很棒啊
That's great.
那或许明天你可以带乔
So, maybe tomorrow, you can take Joe
去参加小男孩公主派对
to that little boy's princess party.
小男孩公主派对吗
Little boy's princess party?
我觉得他也有自由
Eh...I think it's nice that he has the freedom
去扮演任何喜欢的角色啊
to express himself that way.
我很不错吧
Pretty good, huh?
他们要求家长也得变装
They want the parents to go dress up, too.
慢走不送
Okay, I'm out.
弹了45分钟的西塔琴还是没反应
45 minutes of sitar, and nothing.
她这个人听不进别人的话
She can't be reasoned with.
迪迪就是这种人
That's so Dede.
她很明显还在不爽我们
She's clearly still upset with us.
她的确是很记仇
Well, she does hold a grudge.
菲尔
Phil.
克莱尔 能麻烦你帮忙跟你母亲谈谈吗
Claire, could you try and reason with your mother?
什么... 好吧 杰瑞 有没有可能
What -- Okay, Jerry, is it possible
是你把放下她的罪恶感投射在这上面呢
that you are projecting your guilt about moving on?
因为那个才不是我妈妈呢
Because that's not my mom over there.
我不是有意说得那么直接
I don't mean to seem indelicate,
但感觉你现在有点在说疯话呢
but you sound a little crazy right now.
拜托了 跟树谈谈吧
Please, talk to the tree.
好吧
Okay, um...
你好啊 老妈
Hey, uh, Mom?
杰瑞想去墨西哥一年
So, uh...Jerry wants to go to Mexico for a year --
是四个月
Four months!
我就试试 万一呢
Worth a shot.
他很孤单
And he's lonely,
所以他想带上他的新朋友一起去
so he wants to take his new friend.
你说什么
What?
什... 你...
Wh-- You're...
真的吗 你不介意啊
Really? You're okay with it?
她说"玩得愉快"
She says "Have fun."
她是哪种语气
How did she sound?
语气会不会像说反话 绵里藏针
Did she seem passive-aggressive?
对啊 你最好再确认一次吧 克莱尔
Yeah, maybe you should double-check, Claire.
真是太"谢谢"你了 菲尔
Great. Thank you, Phil.
妈 虽然非常想你
Mom, after missing you a lot
而且没有跟你聊过太多别的
and talking about very little else,
但杰瑞遇到了新的对象了
um, Jerry finally met someone.
这个人是迪兰的母亲 法拉
It's -- It's actually Dylan's Mom, Farrah,
杰瑞想带她去墨西哥玩
and he wants to take her to Mexico.
她在听了 接着说
She's listening. Keep going.
杰瑞很担心这么做你会不高兴
Um...Jerry is worried that this would upset you,
但我说你会想看到他开心
but I told him that you want him to be happy
并放下过去往前走 对吧
and to move on, right?
快动啊 快动啊
Please move, please move.
迪迪 晃动是代表"同意"吗
Dede, does the rustling mean "Yes"?
谢谢你 迪迪
Thank you, Dede.
我永远爱你
I will always love you.
我需要来点水
I need some water.
-然后咱们去救那"茄子"吧 -没错
- And let's go rescue that eggplant. - Yes.
真的假的啊
That was crazy!
-你看到了吗 -等等
- Did you see that? - Hold on.
你... 你妈妈还想说点什么
Your -- Your mom wants to say something.
什么
What?
"克莱尔小宝贝
"Hey, Claire Bear.
或许你应该多感激菲尔的魔术
Maybe you should appreciate Phil's magic more,
尤其他刚刚救了你一命"
especially since he just solved your problem."
真是不敢相信 你真是个天才
I can't believe it. You're a genius.
谢谢你
Mm. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
人称我为"线王邓菲"可不是浪得虚名
They don't call me Filament Dunphy for nothing.
真有爱
That is cute,
但你还是会继续卖房子的吧
but you are still selling houses, right?
靠 我20分钟后得带人看房
Oh, shoot, I have a showing in 20 minutes.
爱你
Love you.
看来我应该多给你浇水啊
Oh, I guess I should be watering you more, huh?
我这阵子一直很忙
I've been busy.
你人都不在这
You're not even here,
我都能感觉到你审视的目光
and I feel like you're judging me.
行行行 我没有忙
Fine. I haven't been busy.
我很想你
I miss you.
或许就是因为这样我才不想见到杰瑞
It's probably why I didn't want to see Jerry.
他好容易让我想起你
He reminds me so much of you.
也正是为什么法拉总让我来火
It's also why Farrah drives me nuts.
如果我想要家里有个怪人
If I'm gonna have a kook in my house,
我宁愿要你
I'd want it to be you.
菲尔
Phil.
菲尔 别闹了
Phil, stop it.
老妈你闭嘴啦 我就喜欢这发型
Shut up, Mom. I like this haircut.